Guide to the Frank Clyde Brown papers, 1912-1974 RL.00160
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
- Cylinders and Discs, 10 boxes
  - Phonodiscs, 1936-1941
    - RL00160-PD-0029_01, 1939-08-26 (Box 138, Audio-phonodisc RL00160-PD-0029_01)
      Title: Margaret and William, performer: Palmer, Lora H., location: Senia (N.C.) | Avery County (N.C.), running time: 00:00:57:370
      Title: Lass of Roch Royal, performer: Palmer, Lora H., location: Senia (N.C.) | Avery County (N.C.), running time: 00:00:29:957
      Title: Silver Threads Among Gold, performer: Houston, Mabel | Wiseman, Lola, location: Upper Hinson's Creek, running time: 00:01:15:480
      Title: unknown, performer: Houston, Myron | Wiseman, Bowie, location: North Carolina, running time: 00:01:31:963
      Title: Cumberland Gap, performer: Wiseman, Bowie, location: Upper Hinson's Creek, running time: 00:01:58:573
    - RL00160-PD-0029_02, 1939-08-26 (Box 138, Audio-phonodisc RL00160-PD-0029_02)
      Title: Cackling Hen, performer: Wiseman, Bowie, location: Upper Hinson's Creek, running time: 00:01:10:850
      Title: Humpback Mule, performer: Houston, Myron | Wiseman, Bowie, location: Upper Hinson's Creek, running time: 00:01:28:265
      Title: Don't Forget Me Little Darling, performer: Wiseman, Bowie | Wiseman, Lola | Houston, Mabel | Houston, Myron, location: Upper Hinson's Creek, running time: 00:01:26:067
      Title: Alabama Gals (Buffalo Gals), performer: Houston, Myron | Wiseman, Bowie, location: Upper Hinson's Creek, running time: 00:02:01:805
      Title: Johnson Boys, performer: Houston, Myron | Wiseman, Bowie, location: Upper Hinson's Creek, running time: 00:00:44:833
      Title: Cindy, performer: Houston, Myron | Wiseman, Bowie, location: Upper Hinson's Creek, running time: 00:01:33:490
    - RL00160-PD-0030_01, 1939-08-26 (Box 138, Audio-phonodisc RL00160-PD-0030_01)
      Title: Bury Me 'Neath the Weeping Willow Tree, performer: Wiseman, Bowie | Wiseman, Lola | Houston, Mabel | Houston, Myron, location: Upper Hinson's Creek, running time: 00:02:12:289
      Title: Life is Like a Mountain Railroad, performer: Wiseman, Bowie | Wiseman, Lola | Houston, Mabel | Houston, Myron, location: Upper Hinson's Creek, running time: 00:01:58:183
      Title: Eliza Jane, performer: Wiseman, Bowie | Wiseman, Lola | Houston, Mabel | Houston, Myron, location: Upper Hinson's Creek, running time: 00:01:54:090
      Title: Going Down Road Feeling Bad, performer: Wiseman, Bowie | Wiseman, Lola | Houston, Mabel | Houston, Myron, location: Upper Hinson's Creek, running time: 00:01:54:802
      Title: Honeysuckle Blues [Instrumental], performer: Wiseman, Bowie | Houston, Myron, location: Upper Hinson's Creek, running time: 00:01:16:528
    - RL00160-PD-0030_02, 1939-08-26 (Box 138, Audio-phonodisc RL00160-PD-0030_02)
      Title: Chicken Reel, performer: Wiseman, Lola, location: Upper Hinson's Creek, running time: 00:00:50:252
      Title: Blue Ridge Mountain Home [Harmonica and guitar], performer: Houston, Myron, location: Upper Hinson's Creek, running time: 00:01:10:002
      Title: You Got to See Mother Every Night, performer: Houston, Myron, location: Upper Hinson's Creek, running time: 00:01:08:949
      Title: Coming Round the Mountain [Square dance], performer: Wiseman, Bowie | Houston, Myron, location: Upper Hinson's Creek, running time: 00:01:29:166
      Title: Sourwood Mountain, performer: Wiseman, Bowie | Wiseman, Lola | Houston, Mabel | Houston, Myron, location: Upper Hinson's Creek, running time: 00:00:56:173
      Title: High Top Shoes, performer: Wiseman, Bowie | Wiseman, Lola | Houston, Mabel | Houston, Myron, location: Upper Hinson's Creek, running time: 00:01:13:507
      Title: Old Burke County, performer: Wiseman, Bowie | Wiseman, Lola | Houston, Mabel | Houston, Myron, location: Upper Hinson's Creek, running time: 00:01:09:223
    - RL00160-PD-0031_01, 1939-08-26 (Box 138, Audio-phonodisc RL00160-PD-0031_01)
      Title: Ground Hog, performer: Wiseman, Bowie | Wiseman, Lola | Houston, Mabel | Houston, Myron, location: Upper Hinson's Creek, running time: 00:00:57:593
      Title: Reuben's Train (Train No. 45), performer: Houston, Mabel, location: Upper Hinson's Creek, running time: 00:01:37:724
      Title: Dear Old Southern Home (The Little Log Cabin By the Sea), performer: Wiseman, Lola | Houston, Mabel, location: Upper Hinson's Creek, running time: 00:02:03:999
      Title: Red Wing [instrumental], performer: Wiseman, Bowie | Houston, Mabel | Hicks, Edgar, location: Upper Hinson's Creek, running time: 00:01:32:392
      Title: Yodeling Cowboy, performer: Wiseman, Bowie | Wiseman, Lola | Houston, Mabel | Houston, Myron, location: Upper Hinson's Creek, running time: 00:01:51:358
    - RL00160-PD-0031_02, 1939-08-27 (Box 138, Audio-phonodisc RL00160-PD-0031_02)
      Title: Flitting Away, performer: Hughes, Arizona, location: Upper Hinson's Creek, running time: 00:01:08:891
      Title: unknown, performer: Hughes, Arizona, location: Upper Hinson's Creek, running time: 00:01:47:870
      Title: The Twelve Blessings of Mary, performer: Hughes, Arizona, location: Upper Hinson's Creek, running time: 00:02:26:354
    - RL00160-PD-0032_01, 1939-09-03 (Box 138, Audio-phonodisc RL00160-PD-0032_01)
      Title: Such a Gittin' Up Stairs, performer: Bradley,, location: Blowing Rock (N.C.) | Watauga County (N.C.) | Caldwell County (N.C.), running time: 00:00:17:850
      Title: Blow Gabriel, performer: Bradley,, location: Blowing Rock (N.C.) | Watauga County (N.C.) | Caldwell County (N.C.), running time: 00:01:14:793
      Title: The Tallest Tree In Paradise, performer: Bradley,, location: Blowing Rock (N.C.) | Watauga County (N.C.) | Caldwell County (N.C.), running time: 00:00:28:623
      Title: The Twelve Blessings of Mary, performer: Hughes, Arizona, location: Avery County (N.C.), running time: 00:04:11:623
    - RL00160-PD-0032_02, 1939-09-11 (Box 138, Audio-phonodisc RL00160-PD-0032_02)
      Title: The Little Family (Martha and Mary), performer: Moody, Cynthia, location: Spear (N.C.) | Avery County (N.C.), running time: 00:03:43:983
      Title: The Watchman's Call, performer: Wiseman, Manassa, location: Foot of Buck Hill, running time: 00:01:54:940
      Title: Barbara Allen, performer: Wiseman, Manassa, location: Foot of Buck Hill, running time: 00:01:08:427
      Title: Oh Brother Greene Come to Me (War Song), performer: Greene, Manley, location: Zionville (N.C.) | Watauga County (N.C.), running time: 00:01:25:958
      Title: The Orphan Girl, performer: Greene, Manley, location: Zionville (N.C.) | Watauga County (N.C.), running time: 00:01:36:322
    - RL00160-PD-0033_01, 1939-09-11 (Box 138, Audio-phonodisc RL00160-PD-0033_01)
      Title: The F.F.V. (Wreck of No. 4), performer: Greene, Bessy, location: Zionville (N.C.) | Watauga County (N.C.), running time: 00:04:15:488
      Title: The Silver Dagger (Wake Up You Drowsy Sleeper) (Betsy and Johnny), performer: Greene, Bessy, location: Zionville (N.C.) | Watauga County (N.C.), running time: 00:01:01:735
      Title: Pretty Fair Maid, performer: Greene, Bessy, location: Zionville (N.C.) | Watauga County (N.C.), running time: 00:02:07:971
    - RL00160-PD-0033_02, 1939-09-07 (Box 138, Audio-phonodisc RL00160-PD-0033_02)
      Title: Barbara Allen, performer: Buchanan, H.R., location: Minneapolis (N.C.) | Avery County (N.C.), running time: 00:00:42:795
      Title: Come All Ye Fair and Tender Ladies, performer: Buchanan, H.R., location: Minneapolis (N.C.) | Avery County (N.C.), running time: 00:01:34:451
      Title: Francis Silvers (Franklin), performer: Buchanan, H.R., location: Minneapolis (N.C.) | Avery County (N.C.), running time: 00:04:09:037
      Title: The Little Rosewood Casket, performer: Buchanan, H.R., location: Minneapolis (N.C.) | Avery County (N.C.), running time: 00:00:33:891
      Title: The Little Mohee, performer: Buchanan, H.R., location: Minneapolis (N.C.) | Avery County (N.C.), running time: 00:03:25:160
    - RL00160-PD-0034_01, 1939-12-09 (Box 138, Audio-phonodisc RL00160-PD-0034_01)
      Title: Venison (Hunting Song), performer: Love, Will 'Shorty', location: Durham (N.C.) | Durham County (N.C.), running time: 00:01:28:911
      Title: The Titanic (God Roved On the Waters), performer: Love, Will 'Shorty', location: Durham (N.C.) | Durham County (N.C.), running time: 00:02:37:535
      Title: Oh Lord Search My Heart, performer: Love, Will 'Shorty', location: Durham (N.C.) | Durham County (N.C.), running time: 00:01:57:744
      Title: Old Time Religion, performer: Love, Will 'Shorty', location: Durham (N.C.) | Durham County (N.C.), running time: 00:02:21:547
    - RL00160-PD-0034_02, 1939-12-09 (Box 138, Audio-phonodisc RL00160-PD-0034_02)
      Title: Strange Things Was A-Happening, performer: Love, Will 'Shorty', location: Durham (N.C.) | Durham County (N.C.), running time: 00:02:34:564
      Title: Gimme Oil In My Lamp, performer: Love, Will 'Shorty', location: Durham (N.C.) | Durham County (N.C.), running time: 00:02:26:984
      Title: Christ Was a Weary Traveler, performer: Love, Will 'Shorty', location: Durham (N.C.) | Durham County (N.C.), running time: 00:03:08:460
      Title: Just One Way to the Pearly Gate, performer: Love, Will 'Shorty', location: Durham (N.C.) | Durham County (N.C.), running time: 00:02:06:676
    - RL00160-PD-0035_01, 1940-08-08 (Box 138, Audio-phonodisc RL00160-PD-0035_01)
      Title: The Titanic (Sinking of the Titanic), performer: Lineberger, Nancy, location: Shelby (N.C.) | Cleveland County (N.C.), running time: 00:01:51:116
    - RL00160-PD-0036_01, 1940-06-30 (Box 138, Audio-phonodisc RL00160-PD-0036_01)
      Title: The Frail Wildwood Flowers, performer: Hughes, W.W., location: Jonas Ridge (N.C.) | Burke County (N.C.), running time: 00:01:22:727
      Title: Naomi Wise (John Lewis), performer: Sanders, Eliza, location: Jonas Ridge (N.C.) | Burke County (N.C.), running time: 00:02:52:884
      Title: Leap Frog John, performer: Sanders, Eliza, location: Jonas Ridge (N.C.) | Burke County (N.C.), running time: 00:00:55:081
      Title: Jim Barrier's Murder, performer: Crump, L.B., location: Jonas Ridge (N.C.) | Burke County (N.C.), running time: 00:03:26:381
    - RL00160-PD-0036_02, 1940-07-05 (Box 138, Audio-phonodisc RL00160-PD-0036_02)
      Title: The Frail Wildwood Flowers, performer: Hughes, W.W., location: Jonas Ridge (N.C.) | Burke County (N.C.), running time: 00:01:26:192
      Title: Naomi Wise (John Lewis), performer: Sanders, Eliza, location: Jonas Ridge (N.C.) | Burke County (N.C.), running time: 00:03:47:326
      Title: Leap Frog John, performer: Sanders, Eliza, location: Jonas Ridge (N.C.) | Burke County (N.C.), running time: 00:00:53:127
      Title: Jim Barrier's Murder, performer: Crump, L.B., location: Jonas Ridge (N.C.) | Burke County (N.C.), running time: 00:03:25:119
    - RL00160-PD-0037_01, 1940-07-05 (Box 138, Audio-phonodisc RL00160-PD-0037_01)
      Title: Haunted House [illegible]...with Cat [Prose tale], performer: Crump, L.B., location: Jonas Ridge (N.C.) | Burke County (N.C.), running time: 00:02:03:784
      Title: Tales of Hull Hill, performer: Crump, L.B., location: Jonas Ridge (N.C.) | Burke County (N.C.), running time: 00:04:52:057
      Title: Runt and the Haunted Pine Tree, performer: Crump, L.B., location: Jonas Ridge (N.C.) | Burke County (N.C.), running time: 00:03:18:037
    - RL00160-PD-0037_02, 1940-07-05 (Box 138, Audio-phonodisc RL00160-PD-0037_02)
      Title: The Yaller Bird: Hunting Story [Prose tale], performer: Crump, L.B., location: Jonas Ridge (N.C.) | Burke County (N.C.), running time: 00:03:05:179
      Title: The Vision of Aunt Sallie Simms [Prose tale], performer: Vance, I.D., location: Pineola (N.C.) | Avery County (N.C.), running time: 00:10:01:357
    - RL00160-PD-0038_01, 1940-07-05 (Box 138, Audio-phonodisc RL00160-PD-0038_01)
      Title: The Vision of Aunt Sallie Simms [Prose tale][continued], performer: Vance, I.D., location: Pineola (N.C.) | Avery County (N.C.), running time: 00:03:36:338
      Title: What Caused the Brown Mountain Light, performer: Vance, I.D., location: Pineola (N.C.) | Avery County (N.C.), running time: 00:04:38:922
    - RL00160-PD-0038_02, 1940-07-05 (Box 138, Audio-phonodisc RL00160-PD-0038_02)
      Title: Ghost Story: Mysterious Footsteps, performer: Vance, I.D., location: Pineola (N.C.) | Avery County (N.C.), running time: 00:09:00:739
    - RL00160-PD-0039_01, 1940-07-05 (Box 138, Audio-phonodisc RL00160-PD-0039_01)
      Title: Witch Story: Aunt Dinky Webb and Betty [Prose], performer: Vance, Ira M., location: Pineola (N.C.) | Avery County (N.C.), running time: 00:04:05:630
      Title: Witch Story: Aunt Dinky Webb and Betty's Sweetheart [Prose], performer: Vance, Ira M., location: Pineola (N.C.) | Avery County (N.C.), running time: 00:02:39:399
    - RL00160-PD-0039_02, 1940-07-17 (Box 138, Audio-phonodisc RL00160-PD-0039_02)
      Title: The Model Church, performer: Stamey, Ephraim, location: Altamont (N.C.) | Avery County (N.C.), running time: 00:05:32:684
      Title: And Must I Be to Judgement Brought, performer: Stamey, Ephraim, location: Altamont (N.C.) | Avery County (N.C.), running time: 00:02:14:166
    - RL00160-PD-0040_01, 1940-07-17 (Box 138, Audio-phonodisc RL00160-PD-0040_01)
      Title: The Lone Pilgrim, performer: Stamey, Ephraim | Dellinger, Hestabel, location: Altamont (N.C.) | Avery County (N.C.), running time: 00:02:56:157
      Title: Gypsie Laddie (Gypsy Daisy), performer: Stamey, Ephraim, location: Altamont (N.C.) | Avery County (N.C.), running time: 00:04:00:226
      Title: Pretty Fair Maid (Seven Long Years), performer: Stamey, Ephraim, location: Altamont (N.C.) | Avery County (N.C.), running time: 00:01:13:696
      Title: Young Johnny (O Johnny), performer: Stamey, Ephraim, location: Altamont (N.C.) | Avery County (N.C.), running time: 00:01:36:200
    - RL00160-PD-0040_02, 1940-07-14 (Box 138, Audio-phonodisc RL00160-PD-0040_02)
      Title: The Old Man, performer: Stamey, Ephraim, location: Altamont (N.C.) | Avery County (N.C.), running time: 00:01:14:349
      Title: Little Bunch of Roses, performer: Stamey, Ephraim, location: Altamont (N.C.) | Avery County (N.C.), running time: 00:00:53:047
      Title: Froggie Went A-Courtin', performer: Stamey, Ephraim, location: Altamont (N.C.) | Avery County (N.C.), running time: 00:01:37:916
      Title: Lord Thomas and Fair Annet, performer: Stamey, Ephraim, location: Altamont (N.C.) | Avery County (N.C.), running time: 00:00:53:453
      Title: The Skeptic's Daughter, performer: Stamey, Ephraim, location: Altamont (N.C.) | Avery County (N.C.), running time: 00:01:01:483
      Title: The Waggoner Lad (Driver's Boy), performer: Stamey, Ephraim, location: Altamont (N.C.) | Avery County (N.C.), running time: 00:00:14:060
      Title: The Wagonner Lad, performer: Stamey, Ephraim, location: Altamont (N.C.) | Avery County (N.C.), running time: 00:00:35:179
      Title: The Waggoner Lad, performer: Dellinger, Hestabel, location: Altamont (N.C.) | Avery County (N.C.), running time: 00:00:47:080
    - RL00160-PD-0041_01, 1940-07-14 (Box 138, Audio-phonodisc RL00160-PD-0041_01)
      Title: The Faithful Lovers, performer: Dellinger, Hestabel, location: Altamont (N.C.) | Avery County (N.C.), running time: 00:01:26:187
      Title: Little Rosewood Casket, performer: Dellinger, Hestabel | Stamey, Ephraim, location: Altamont (N.C.) | Avery County (N.C.), running time: 00:02:48:626
      Title: Ole Smokey (Old Smoky), performer: Johnson, Obadiah (Obie), location: Crossnore (N.C.) | Avery County (N.C.), running time: 00:01:52:944
      Title: Come All Ye Fair and Tender Ladies, performer: Johnson, Obadiah (Obie), location: Crossnore (N.C.) | Avery County (N.C.), running time: 00:01:55:942
    - RL00160-PD-0041_02, 1940-07-14 (Box 138, Audio-phonodisc RL00160-PD-0041_02)
      Title: Seven Long Years I've Been Married, performer: Johnson, Obadiah (Obie), location: Crossnore (N.C.) | Avery County (N.C.), running time: 00:01:22:437
      Title: Great Grandad, performer: Johnson, Obadiah (Obie), location: Crossnore (N.C.) | Avery County (N.C.), running time: 00:01:17:946
      Title: I Wonder As I Wander, performer: Johnson, Obadiah (Obie), location: Crossnore (N.C.) | Avery County (N.C.), running time: 00:02:27:576
      Title: Housekeeper's Tragedy, performer: Johnson, Obadiah (Obie), location: Crossnore (N.C.) | Avery County (N.C.), running time: 00:02:37:482
    - RL00160-PD-0042_01, 1940-08-08 (Box 138, Audio-phonodisc RL00160-PD-0042_01)
      Title: Old Woman, performer: Burleson, Clarice (Claire) | Powles, Joe, location: Crossnore (N.C.) | Avery County (N.C.), running time: 00:01:22:781
      Title: Hole In the Bucket, performer: Burleson, Clarice (Claire) | Powles, Joe, location: Crossnore (N.C.) | Avery County (N.C.), running time: 00:03:30:772
      Title: Billy Boy, performer: Burleson, Clarice (Claire) | Powles, Joe, location: Crossnore (N.C.) | Avery County (N.C.), running time: 00:01:14:173
      Title: Paper of Pins, performer: Burleson, Clarice (Claire) | Powles, Joe, location: Crossnore (N.C.) | Avery County (N.C.), running time: 00:01:40:144
    - RL00160-PD-0042_02, 1940-08-08 (Box 138, Audio-phonodisc RL00160-PD-0042_02)
      Title: Captain Wedderburn's Courtship (Riddle Song), performer: Johnson, Obadiah (Obie), location: Crossnore (N.C.) | Avery County (N.C.), running time: 00:01:16:106
      Title: Ground Hog, performer: Johnson, Obadiah (Obie), location: Crossnore (N.C.) | Avery County (N.C.), running time: 00:00:54:114
      Title: Frog Went A-Courtin', performer: Burleson, Clarice (Claire), location: Crossnore (N.C.) | Avery County (N.C.), running time: 00:01:02:138
      Title: Grandma Grunts, performer: Burleson, Clarice (Claire) | Powles, Joe, location: Crossnore (N.C.) | Avery County (N.C.), running time: 00:01:00:629
      Title: Possum Up a Simmon Tree, performer: Burleson, Clarice (Claire) | Powles, Joe, location: Crossnore (N.C.) | Avery County (N.C.), running time: 00:00:57:143
    - RL00160-PD-0043_01, 1940-08-08 (Box 138, Audio-phonodisc RL00160-PD-0043_01)
      Title: Square Dance Figures, performer: Carolina Ramblers | Greer, John, location: Boone (N.C.) | Watauga County (N.C.), running time: 00:02:24:516
      Title: Dance Tune, performer: Carolina Ramblers | Greer, John, location: Boone (N.C.) | Watauga County (N.C.), running time: 00:01:00:690
      Title: Frog Went A' Courtin', performer: York, James, location: Boone (N.C.) | Watauga County (N.C.), running time: 00:02:14:833
      Title: Poor Tommy, performer: York, James, location: Boone (N.C.) | Watauga County (N.C.), running time: 00:00:11:536
      Title: Poor Willie (Sinful to Flirt), performer: Ward, Sena, location: Reidsville (N.C.) | Rockingham County (N.C.), running time: 00:00:48:663
      Title: Pretty Fair Maid, performer: Ward, Sena, location: Reidsville (N.C.) | Rockingham County (N.C.), running time: 00:00:25:861
      Title: Frog Went A' Courtin', performer: Eggers, Herman A., location: Boone (N.C.) | Watauga County (N.C.), running time: 00:02:27:578
    - RL00160-PD-0043_02, 1940-08-08 (Box 138, Audio-phonodisc RL00160-PD-0043_02)
      Title: The Girl I Love Won't Pay Me No Mind, performer: Carolina Ramblers, location: Boone (N.C.) | Watauga County (N.C.), running time: 00:01:48:546
      Title: Rising Sun, performer: Carolina Ramblers | McMahair, Ed, location: Boone (N.C.) | Watauga County (N.C.), running time: 00:01:35:994
      Title: Ain't It Hard to Love a Girl that Don't Love You, performer: Carolina Ramblers, location: Boone (N.C.) | Watauga County (N.C.), running time: 00:00:38:371
      Title: One Old Shirt, performer: Carolina Ramblers | Story, Carl, location: Boone (N.C.) | Watauga County (N.C.), running time: 00:01:52:418
      Title: Old Age Pension Check, performer: Carolina Ramblers | Story, Carl, location: Boone (N.C.) | Watauga County (N.C.), running time: 00:01:52:418
      Title: Not Letter In the Mail, performer: Carolina Ramblers | Story, Carl, location: Boone (N.C.) | Watauga County (N.C.), running time: 00:01:53:618
    - RL00160-PD-0044_01, 1940-08-08 (Box 138, Audio-phonodisc RL00160-PD-0044_01)
      Title: Little Mary Fagin, performer: Rives, location: Boone (N.C.) | Watauga County (N.C.), running time: 00:00:47:183
      Title: Freight Train Blues, performer: Carolina Ramblers, location: Boone (N.C.) | Watauga County (N.C.), running time: 00:02:32:694
      Title: Up Jumped the Devil, performer: Carolina Ramblers, location: Boone (N.C.) | Watauga County (N.C.), running time: 00:00:58:625
      Title: Lord Ullin's Daughter, performer: York, James, location: Boone (N.C.) | Watauga County (N.C.), running time: 00:00:42:661
      Title: Georgie, performer: York, James, location: Boone (N.C.) | Watauga County (N.C.), running time: 00:00:27:275
      Title: Georgie [Her Little Mohee air], performer: York, James, location: Boone (N.C.) | Watauga County (N.C.), running time: 00:01:17:940
    - RL00160-PD-0044_02, 1940-08-08 (Box 138, Audio-phonodisc RL00160-PD-0044_02)
      Title: Gypsie Laddie (Gypsy Davy), performer: York, James, location: Boone (N.C.) | Watauga County (N.C.), running time: 00:00:13:323
      Title: Pretty Polly, performer: York, James, location: Boone (N.C.) | Watauga County (N.C.), running time: 00:00:25:518
      Title: Pretty Polly [Second air], performer: York, James, location: Boone (N.C.) | Watauga County (N.C.), running time: 00:00:30:633
      Title: Lady Isabel and the Elf Knight (The Seven King's Daughters), performer: York, James, location: Boone (N.C.) | Watauga County (N.C.), running time: 00:00:37:725
      Title: Maid Freed From the Gallows, performer: York, James, location: Boone (N.C.) | Watauga County (N.C.), running time: 00:00:25:039
      Title: The Lady and the Sailor, performer: York, James, location: Boone (N.C.) | Watauga County (N.C.), running time: 00:03:13:300
      Title: Goldie Locks', performer: York, James, location: Boone (N.C.) | Watauga County (N.C.), running time: 00:03:00:763
    - RL00160-PD-0045_01, 1940-08-08 (Box 138, Audio-phonodisc RL00160-PD-0045_01)
      Title: The Ditch of Briars, performer: York, James, location: Boone (N.C.) | Watauga County (N.C.), running time: 00:03:28:410
      Title: This Old Man, performer: Timmons, Laura B., location: Boone (N.C.) | Watauga County (N.C.), running time: 00:01:27:566
      Title: Wife Wrapped In Wether's Skin, performer: York, James, location: Boone (N.C.) | Watauga County (N.C.), running time: 00:01:50:280
      Title: Come All Ye Young Ladies, performer: York, James, location: Boone (N.C.) | Watauga County (N.C.), running time: 00:01:51:483
      Title: Little Musgrove and Lady Bernard (Little Matthy Groves), performer: York, James, location: Boone (N.C.) | Watauga County (N.C.), running time: 00:00:19:467
    - RL00160-PD-0045_02, 1940-08-08 (Box 138, Audio-phonodisc RL00160-PD-0045_02)
      Title: Old English Hunting Song, performer: York, James, location: Boone (N.C.) | Watauga County (N.C.), running time: 00:01:10:541
      Title: Barbara Allen, performer: York, James, location: Boone (N.C.) | Watauga County (N.C.), running time: 00:00:17:713
      Title: The Farmer's Curst Wife, performer: York, James, location: Boone (N.C.) | Watauga County (N.C.), running time: 00:00:53:155
      Title: Scolding Wife, performer: York, James, location: Boone (N.C.) | Watauga County (N.C.), running time: 00:01:05:209
      Title: Barbara Allen, performer: York, James, location: Boone (N.C.) | Watauga County (N.C.), running time: 00:00:40:788
      Title: London City, performer: Walker, Edith, location: Boone (N.C.) | Watauga County (N.C.), running time: 00:00:28:159
      Title: The Willow Garden, performer: Walker, Edith, location: Boone (N.C.) | Watauga County (N.C.), running time: 00:00:29:865